foreign
[Music]
universe
alrighty bro are you ready on the count
of three
one
two four seven
wait bro do you not know how to count
[Music]
who yet happy birthday looks now you are
finally the same age as us
well until we have our next birthday
damn it manic you got rainbow confetti
in my birthday pudding
do you see manic I told you these Party
Poppers were a gay ass idea I bet you
feel pretty stupid now that you didn't
settle for a cool party hat from Party
City like me and Trevor
oh [__] I'm sorry man
no you're not fool you knew how much I
was looking forward to this pudding and
now it's ruined now I must ask you bye
for what purpose are you targeting
Knuckles the cool echidna
but I wasn't why would I ever attack the
birthday boy don't say anything more
gunks you already [__] up one time
today now you only get two more shots
till we send you home
I will have you no [__] that my grandpa
woke up 10 minutes early to hide it in
My Lunchbox for a nice little treat
you didn't just attack my birthday you
would act my heart
come on Knuckles it's your birthday
lighten up and have some fun
do I look like I'm having fun no on the
contrary it should be a day of fear
for it marks the Mirai Knuckles the cool
Echidna was born into the world yeah
yeah destined to make everyone else's
life's worse just by being an
unparalleled badass yeah you know anyone
else who can dig in the ground with
their bare hands no or someone who can't
miss 18 yards into the air while laying
on their back no who invited those
[__] babies that's what I thought now
get that apple green candy ass out of my
sight
and fetch me another pudding from
Walgreens please
stalling go on and give it to him
I think I'll wait a bit there's still so
many people around
Sonia
how long are you going to keep running
he's one of the popular kids everyone
knows they travel in bags
I doubt you will be able to catch him
alone the whole day
just go on over there and get it over
with
but but what if something goes wrong
what if they taste weird and
I'm sure they taste lovely you were up
practicing making truffles every night
and besides if he laughs he'll have to
answer to me
I'll tell you what if it will make you
feel better I'll just go give it to him
myself and tell him it was from you but
be warned I can't promise you I won't
force him to let me suck his balls
I can't do that that will just make it
look like I'm avoiding him
and will you stop threatening to suck
his balls no
no hi girls are we discussing truffles
today
did you make those for knuckles
I wish people would stop giving those
nasty little things as gifts they're
often so better that I end up throwing
them away most of the time
oh you you cut your hair
oh no does it look weird oh I I knew I
shouldn't have done it myself I only
wanted to change things up for once
maybe it was a bad idea
yeah it does
no no you look okay
really thanks I was worried about what
you might say bye I think you look the
pretty today too Sonia actually you're
always so pretty you're a curly hair
reminds me of strawberry shortcakes
what's in the box [__] you better not
be swiping up Marcus to sniff them in
the bathroom between second and third
period again oh this it's nothing
they're just some of the spare lemon and
cranberries cones from my shops that
didn't sell too well I refuse to give
handouts to the homeless as I believe
rewards should come to those who work
and rather than toss them in a bin I
thought Knuckles might like them it's
his birthday I hear does he like the
sweets
for those chocolate truffles ugh I hope
you're not planning on giving those to
him I always forget how awful they taste
so I'll have one spit it out about not
eat them again yet they somehow have a
Stranglehold on the holiday and birthday
Market it really is quite odd
oh are we heading somewhere in that case
can we stop by my locker first I need my
flip-flops and knee pads
Flora just drop it
but I'm not holding anything
you know what I mean stop to open to my
friends
but there are friends
look I know Dad wants us to get along
especially since you found an apartment
with a window pointing directly towards
my bedroom
but we just don't click you know what I
mean
not really
then let me put it in a way you can
understand
you are like the sudden need to take a
[__] certain places and times can make
this worse but there is really no time
when a person likes having to poop
why Mindy why would you say something
like that
it's true we all hate you we don't talk
about you like at all in fact we go out
of our way to exclude you if at all
possible you are like the female version
of Trevor
who's clever
don't you have your own friend group of
six people with specific traits
no no I already said those ones are mine
why don't we share him you can't have
them on Monday and Tuesday and I get
them the rest of the week for that to
happen they would have to want to hang
out with you and you have small tits
[__] hell watch where you're walking
dumb ass
you almost made me drop this chocolate
pudding from Dollar Tree
did you say Dollar Tree
I asked for Walgreens I'm gonna beat
your ass
oh my gosh I'm so sorry I'll be more
careful next time
shut up [__] talk to the ass
come on nux pull down your pants it's
time for your 15 birthday spankings
Bro Look chicken nuggets
those aren't chicken nuggets bro they're
British scones
I recognize the size and shape because
it was something bartlebby made me eat
straight out of his butthole after
hirana cross-country Marathon
haha bro you and Bartleby are such crazy
lovers
wait wait those are meant for you the
are supposed to be a present for
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my God there's blood splurking out of
his butt bro they're pulling out their
phones don't let them film this
bro bro help me I am dying
I need some Coca-Cola and some of those
microwavable chicken patties you this is
your fault what the hell did you put in
those scones
not much maybe some cranberries and some
lemon zest
lemon what the [__] is that is that some
kind of vegetable
my brother can only eat processed foods
you could have killed him you know
bro I see it I see the light Angels they
really do exist
they're so [__] sexy
don't go Sonic don't go towards the
light
but he's beckoning me beckoning with the
sound of his clapping cheeks
[Music]
all right
I simply can't thank you enough for the
help today Bartleby we were in desperate
need of someone to play the angel in my
new music video and I couldn't imagine
someone more fitting for the part than
you
don't mention it Jesse McCartney I know
you would have done the same for me yes
handsome light boys got to stick
together
haha yeah anyway since we're on break
now I made us some grilled cheese
sandwiches we would like to eat them
together with me I bet you're famished
after all that hard work more grilled
cheeses my Jesse I'm starting to get the
idea you don't care about this music
video at all
did you perhaps make this all up just to
have an excuse to get close to this
school
where my big Sonic the Hedgehog studies
all in the slim chance that you could
watch him and I duck
haha oh beitelby looks like you caught
me again but I will catch you two
[__] eventually it should be illegal
for someone so sexy as you to get away
with doing it unseen even in the privacy
of your home home how dare you deny the
people what they want you piece of
garbage
why do you think I was caught hiding by
your bedside window in the middle of the
night two months ago I was there
listening to the sounds of your hairy
balls slapping against your [__] but
crack as though you were going to town
on some Denny's pancakes oh yes that was
the time I farted on you
I'll see that hidden wonder of the world
someday you can [__] count on that
[__] I swear to God in hell
Jesse I think it's time for you to go
and take this girl's cheers with you I
bet it's not even cheese but your own
congealed piss settled nicely between
two slices of Wonder Bread
curses foil twice today
oh I'm so embarrassed I better call Dad
and have him come pick me up hopefully
he'll remember he has a third daughter
this time wait this isn't mine my phone
is a flip phone
oh
that phone
oh Sonia die I didn't see you there is
there something you needed
as a matter of fact there is I want to
know why you think it's cool to sneak
around the library with stolen property
like a Mexican
stolen what are you talking about no you
mean this this this phone is mine
you really expect anyone to believe that
[__]
I guess your brother and I have similar
tastes
where did you buy those Monster stickers
what you heard what I said and that
phone case I want to know where you got
it and when
I was alone
yeah I bet you were when the principal
hears about this your butt is grass
but that's not I wasn't you're being so
weird right now I bought this with my
own money
manic you're the one who told me about
this one right you told me where to buy
it you said it right tell her
gross did a [__] just touch me get away
from me you weirdo up associate
oh gosh is it time for class already
I'll see you around like a donut
I'm sorry did you perchance think you
could Escape judgment
your beautiful Flora you always were
why don't you fess up and tell me what
you're really after
otherwise I'll spread what you did all
throughout the school
but I I wasn't trying to do anything you
have it all wrong
why did you really cut your hair today
and on uncle's birthday
were you trying to take the attention
away from him are you that desperate for
admiration
why were you deleting pictures of me
from manic's phone
is it really all due to jealousy do
other people being happily get to you
that much
I'm not jealous you're being weird again
I'm weird
you're the one who always wears a happy
face when you're clearly miserable
you're breaking and you don't know what
to do about it others might not be able
to see or rather they couldn't even be
bothered to look
turning their gaze towards the direction
of someone as pathetic as you would be
one big waste of time
[Music]
seriously I don't understand how scum
like you are allowed to walk around free
in our society you are always a bit of
an outsider even amongst mobians never
as smart as the rest of us
too Spacey to be Dependable as a freedom
fighter frankly I don't see anywhere you
fit in I'm surprised you haven't killed
yourself yet maybe you should it's not
like anyone would miss you Mendy
wouldn't recognize you've gone I don't
even think Knuckles learned your name
let's chart down a Time
I'll even help you do it oh wait the way
you are you would find a way to ruin
that too
[Music]
did that hurt I thought this is what you
wanted
now you have all the attention
[Music]
you think I wanted this don't pretend
like you know anything about me I grew
up with two hormonally balanced sisters
where stuff like this was the north
constantly judging me for not being
perfect pushing me around like they knew
better and letting me know how much cute
they were and how much Dumber I was we
all have our issues but it's your job to
make sure your own doesn't affect the
rest
much I suffered how much I had to put up
with
Flora stop it what has overtaken your
ass
Get Your Filthy Hands off of me slat you
are a thief who stole everything for me
my home my family when will you finally
get out of my life
[Applause]
get the hell off of me you wild animal
who the hell are you to call anyone a
thief
foreign
that [__] in the overalls is oatmeal
cray-cray what a shitty [__] mess
whose principal fat butts at a time like
this
goddamn that blue girl got totally
stomped she couldn't even get one hit in
don't laugh she might come after you
next what it's fun absolutely
what's with the liqueur you wanna go
again
are you satisfied now that you made me a
laughing stock in front of everyone
oh shut up you make it sound like this
is all my fault
what happened to the quiet version of
you from yesterday
weren't you better off like that
who cares she was nothing but a loser
if she was a loser then what are you
I wonder what she'd think if she saw you
now
good
[Music]
foreign
so come on if you're a loser you should
act like one
drink from the puddle like a dog
[Music]
the child who resorted to running away
from home is a minor to escape the abuse
by the toxic family
all those hours spent gazing into the
mirror seeing the irreparable damage why
would I care what she thinks
honestly I'm happier than I've ever been
if this is how you want it then I won't
stop you
but I won't be there for you either
[Music]
you'll go through the rest of your life
alone only this time you won't have
anyone to blame
[Music]
Debbie look over there it's that bastard
they called you smelly
is it now well Nick I think it's time we
pay our tubby friend Sonic the Hedgehog
visit
hell yeah Dylan you're the boss
I know now don't talk anymore today
unless I tell YouTube [__]
look who it is if it isn't the one and
only smelly Devon the smelliest guy in
gym class because he doesn't put on
deodorant after running laps in gym
class
shut up you know I was just too poor to
buy any deal then
the cause my dad left me and my mum
alone for gay man yeah now he goes by
sexy given Nick shut up I was just about
to let him know that let me defend my
own honor
sexy Devin Hub since when
since I got sexy by dying my hair yellow
and started wearing a brown shirt now
stop interrupting me or the ones coming
at you right now
what are you doing in my lunch break
spot
I don't see your name on it
if you need to know I'm meeting my
boyfriend here
so we can eat some pretty Bots Every
Flavor jelly beans
jelly beans instead of M M's you some
kind of a [__] or some [__]
a little bit but mostly because it's
just fun thing to do you don't know what
flavor you are going to get when you eat
one cause for example Berry Blue has the
same color as toothpaste
shut up everyone knows howberty Bots
every flavor beans work
hey my shirt is blue too
Nick shut up
you never let me do anything
I think you need a bit of an interest to
remember your place
do you know what sexy Devon I'm not
going to take this harassment you two
lovebirds can just have this seat I bet
you guys [__] on it all the time anyway
that's probably why it smells like crap
so what if we do
Nick what part of shut up don't you
understand
the first part
anyway I have this gun so follow us
and leave your phone so Bartle be kept
track and murder us while we move you to
the next location
or we may or may not put a bullet in
your [__] skull
hey before we do that given can I eat
out his butthole it's not every day you
find someone with a tushy like this one
no don't you dare touch his butt in any
sexual way
if we do get caught I want it to be for
murder I may take someone's life in Cold
Blood but rape is where I draw the line
now hurry up Jesse McCartney is over
there for some reason
and I don't want him to see us doing
evil Deeds
dear God it smells like rotten eggs and
mayonnaise in here
thanks welcome to your new home freak
oh yeah fart again boy oh it tricks out
two different jelly beans
[Music]
hey Devon I want to make him fart for me
now
your job is to just stand there looking
menacing
I hate this I never get to say anything
that's because you never had anything
worth saying Yoon income poop
I do I do have worth in my life prove it
then say something clever
I I can't think of anything right now
you see
that's not fair how would you like it if
I put you on the spot it's not as easy
as it looks Steven you're you're just
being a nasty bully I can see why they
once called you smelly didn't cause your
heartbreaks of Cruelty
that's it I'm going to give you another
nipple twist no you won't in case you
haven't noticed I'm standing on a
GameCube you can't reach me from this
height I learned your tricks you're
never going to beat me again
not if I shoot you in the face get with
the hostage [__]
sorry Sonic I tried
I know you did Nick
okay Sonic call your boyfriend Bart Levy
tell him to come here's app my boyfriend
isn't that a bit counter-intuitive to
what you asked of me before
I have different plans now so call your
lover and when you do ask him no begged
him to [__] your ass
while me and Nick High behind those Xbox
series X game consoles we try to scalp
online but can't get rid of since
everybody wants a PlayStation 5 instead
we're going to film you and Bart will be
having sex because it's so hot
your goal is to watch me and my
boyfriend have sex
but why would you eat
there he is don't let him get away
answer me
a hint of cinnamon some Gilly weeds
oh I have boot a powerful ingredient in
potion brewing but nothing uncommon
oh what have we here is that the right
stand should put cracked hairs and
Reese's Peanut Butter Cups yup it's a
poly juice potion all right
now we know who's been stealing from
your storage service
so who has an idea of this man's true
identity
if I was a betting man I would say it's
my evil okay Nazi lover Grindelwald
but I thought Grindelwald was back at
Hogwarts dueling the Weasley boy
it is over for you greater Walt I Ronald
Weasley will be the end of you
I have to say it you must have balls of
steel if you really want to go against
me
and trust me when I say that I know my
boss you shut your pie hole IM the best
friend of [__] Harry Potter
[__] if he was here right now he would
have you on the ground begging for mercy
but I'm not like him no I will give you
no mercy I'm going to beat the [__] out
of you up in this piece of ass fighting
somebody else's battle her pathetic
you're nothing but badoo's personal
[__] ha you make that sound like a bad
thing never said it was
laughs
it appears that I may have
underestimated your abilities
it's clear that I do not have the
magical prowess to defeat euron Weasley
Dumbledore was smart to send you to me I
wonder just who is the real [__] in the
relationship you or Harry
either way I'm getting the hell out of
here see you around [__] luminous
[Music]
by the gods I'll let granddaughter Walt
get away I better report back to
Dumbledore in a jiffy
[Music]
that was a close one luckily I was able
to Blind him long enough to escape
now since I'm gay I'll hide in the girls
bathroom until I think of my next plan
they won't expect me to go in the girls
bathroom because I'm gay
oh right then I bet it's a black person
then you would only be half right
Dumbledore
because he's only acting like one
he thought he could play a soul for
fools simply because he got his dirty
hands on a poly juice potion but it
didn't work on me you may have changed
looks on the outside Jesse but on the
inside you're just as much the sick and
twisted pervert you always were
Oh look The Polyjuice Potions effects
appear to be wearing off
[Applause]
I don't believe it it's Jesse McCartney
the mid-2000s teenage pop star
that's right and I would have gotten
away with it it weren't for Bartleby
being so good at everything
wait a minute but if he's Jesse then
what happened to given me and Devan both
saw Jesse McCartney over by the school
playground
there is no Devon Nick
and that wasn't Jesse
you must not be fooled by a cardboard
cutout of the famous pop star
indeed four months ago the teenage heart
drum pop star Jesse McCartney
infiltrated Sonics Middle School
plotting to catch Sonic and Bartleby in
the act of making sweet love to one
another thankfully we caught wind not
too long ago
I see well it's a little embarrassing
having to be saved by you once again my
love may I have a ride in your limo I
need to get back to school
hold on my Teletubby I think after the
day you had you deserve a break or
should I say a good nasty [__] hahaha we
can go over there behind those shitty
game consoles and you can suck my balls
I'll give you four dollars if you let me
watch
care for this name as a professor of
Hogwarts it would be very unfortunate if
two grown as men like a sore scene
watching children have sex which is what
I would say if I didn't want to also
haha I guess now we know why they call
you the Headmaster
yeah it's because I'm a really good
wizard
or it's because you suck dick no I'm
just really good
[Music]
yellow
hello would this be Miss Hedgehog
I don't pay taxes
this is principal fat butts from your
children's Middle School I'm calling to
discuss issues involving your daughter
can you speed this up I'm busy watching
my brother play in the sprinklers so he
doesn't drowning
shut up Charles you don't pay the bills
didn't you hear me before I don't want
to give you a minute
are you an Asian because you sound like
one ching chong ping pong sorry that
probably sounded racist
what I have to tell you is very
important news regarding your daughter
so listen carefully I'm afraid she's
being suspended from school for three
days due to a fight she had with another
student
did she win well she isn't too terribly
injured did she win my current
understanding of the incident indicates
that your daughter through the first
punch
foreign
did I just hear you high five to the
Beatdown of another student Miss Alina
Miss Hedgehog are you even listening to
me
today foreign
sorry I spaced out for a second there
what were we talking about
I Allure you to take this more seriously
this could be a very bad Mark if she
plans on going to college
sorry I got a little carried away oh
that doesn't sound like my baby
are you sure you're not getting her
mixed up with my other neon colored
Hedgehog lips they're triplets and
basically just we colors of each other
kind of like how they're just small
recolored versions of me
oh I'm sure she's sitting with me now
would you like to speak to her
I'm so sorry Mama I beat her up I hurt
Flora really [__] bad
I made her my [__] [__]
Sonia I really don't give a damn about
that [__] tonight I'm going to make your
favorite
broccoli and cauliflower rumlet with a
loaf of wheat bread on the side and an
ice cold glass of cream soda with
vanilla bean ice cream
maybe I'll even bring out the grape
juice so you can act like a drinking
wine like a big girl we really wow Mom I
thought you would be mad
I worship the rain that Waters the grass
that grows on the ground you walk on
your uncle and I are over the moon the
two stood up for yourself instead of
taking it like a [__]
wait for me by the school Gates I'll
swing around by to pick you up
can can you bring those cute Band-Aids
with the smiley faces on them
of course anything for you cornbread
[Music]
hey Sonia you okay
Knuckles don't don't come over here you
don't want to be seen with me I made
myself look like a total fool today
what I don't think so at all you're not
the one who shows up to class every day
in purple overalls and orange stripes
but I I really hurt her
who cares it's her fault for pissing you
the [__] off
besides I'm sure everyone will forget it
happened by the weekend
but Sonic and manic they're never going
to let me live it down I never got into
trouble at school before
we all thought it would be manichude
fail at life I feel so dirty
do you think I was being too cruel with
the things I said
no way I saw what happened no one will
consider it your fault when they find
out she went through Maddox phone
you defended his ass and that deserves
respect
someone like her who always plays the
victim it always goes like this
maybe you actually knock some sense into
her
speaking of which I I could be wrong but
I think I got more hits in
yeah you really did you did great
I'll be your dream I'll be your wish
[Music]
you don't have to say anything if you
don't want to
I'm pretty comfortable with the
relationship we have now
sorry
[Music]
it seems like I lied
any minute now
[Music]
although you are sweetie you really know
how to keep a lady waiting
I'll Make A Wish send it to Heaven that
make you want to cry
to cry as of joy for all the pleasure
Charles West my bell oh no
protection of the highest power and
Lonely Hour the tears divide
you I wanna stand with you on a mountain
[Music]
oh can't you see it baby you don't have
to close your eyes
[Music]
I
wanna play
[Music]
I can't believe we get to eat chicken
tindies with mashed potatoes and gravy
three days in a row
I know can you believe there are
actually people out there who think
school lunch sucks
they must be third worlders from Iraq
hey Sonia I'll trade you two of my baby
turrets for your entire tray of food
no thanks
did you just say No [__] I'm the leader
of our band you don't get to defy me but
bro we haven't released a new album in
years because you're too lazy
just for saying that I'm getting yours
too [__]
[__] you sis now I don't get any chicken
tendies either this is the third time
this week this happened
whatever let's just figure this out when
we sit down
oh great come on Sonic Underground let's
go find another place for me to eat your
food it smells like there's an [__]
over there
I'll catch up with you two in a minute
there's something I gotta take care of
first
oh I get it you're going to steal her
food to give to me you're such a
supportive sister
come on manic let's go steal another
student's potato salad
[Music]
hey Flora would you mind if I sit down
I don't wanna hate you
me either
Flora what was that about last week
I've never seen you go off like that
before
you already know why
Flora it's just like you said I was
jealous I always was
since the first day I saw you I could
see a dignified Lick in your eyes well
past my own you looked like a girl who
was blessed with everything in the world
you seemed to have nothing to worry
about and yet you looked like you were
always concerned about something that's
why I grew to despise you it was
jealousy an admiration I wanted to hate
you because you already have the
treasures that I could never have
friends a caring mother
siblings who love you
[Music]
so everything you did
I saw the way Knuckles looks at you so I
decided to cut my hair I deleted your
pictures and tried to break your friend
group apart by trying to take your place
I only lost a piece of myself I really
am the worst of the worst
Flora you don't have to try and be
anybody else
we all love you Just the Way You Are
but I made a terrible mistake and I
wasn't born White
my mom always said it's not the mistake
that defines Who You Are
but what you do after that is what
really matters
[Music]
moms are great I wish mine wasn't
murdered by my own sister in Cold Blood
for not letting her get a boob job
I wonder where she is now last time I
heard she was in Costa Rica getting
plastic surgery in an alleyway
but I guess that's what sex before
marriage does to a person
hey Sonia someday if it's possible can
can we become friends again
we always were
[Music]
I don't know my mind
let me down
[Music]